Open your heart. Find your voice.
Song for Marion is a music, comedy, romance film
directed by Paul Andrew Williams.
Arthur is a grumpy pensioner who can't understand why his wife Marion would want to
embarrass herself singing silly songs with her unconventional local choir.
But choir director Elizabeth sees something special in the
reluctant Arthur and refuses to give up on him.
As she coaxes him out of his shell, Arthur realizes
that it is never too late to change.
Arthur, played by Terence Stamp.
Marion, played by Vanessa Redgrave.
Elizabeth, played by Gemma Arterton.
James, played by Christopher Eccleston.
Brenda, played by Anne Reid.
Charlie, played by Ram John Holder.
Song for Marion is a 2012 British-German comedy-drama film written and directed by Paul Andrew Williams
and starring Terence Stamp, Gemma Arterton, Christopher Eccleston and Vanessa Redgrave.
The film was released as Unfinished Song in the USA.
The film was nominated for three awards—Best Actor, Best Screenplay, and Best
Supporting Actress—at the 2012 British Independent Film Awards.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.